

Cyrelle DeCou

510-282-2653 www.cyrelle.cl cyrellophane@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/cyrelle

About Me

I am an Oakland-based digital creative with more then 10 years of experience and offering a versatile skill set. My passion is for all things visual and how they interact with people and their lives, which motivates me to create work that connects with my audience.

Currently, I am looking to join forces with a great team in the print or web design community. I am seeking a role and position where my skills can be fully tested, fostered, and utilized.

Skills

Design concepts

- Visual communication in multiple mediums
- Strong understanding of best practices for color, typography, and composition
- E-commerce marketing and UI design
- · Print processes and pre-flight
- Production and asset management
- · Product photography and image editing

Expert level software

Adobe Creative Cloud: Photoshop / InDesign / Illustrator / Acrobat / Bridge / Typekit

Other Software/Services

Squarespace / Sketch / Mailchimp / Atom

Basic web coding skills

Office productivity software

Word / Excel / Powerpoint / JIRA

Teamwork

- · Working to deadlin
- Mentorship of junior designers
- Strong team ethic

Experience

Senior Visual Designer Delivery Agent 2007 – 2016 Created engaging and compelling website, email, and promotional materials (print and web) from concept to launch for various clients including:

Discovery Channel NBC Jessica Simpson **Dunkin Donuts** Oprah ABC 1791 Supply and Co. Rachel Ray HBO UFC Fox Stand Up 2 Cancer Playboy FΧ History Channel The Simpsons **Boston Celtics** Showtime A&E Pepsi Food Network New York Knicks CBS Bravo

- Managed a workload of creating five web store launches as well as my day-to-day promotional work in less than 3 months and delivered everything on time.
- · Provided mentorship and training to junior designers, contractors, and interns.
- Developed branding guidelines and templates for new clients including: Oprah, Jessica Simpson, Stand Up 2 Cancer, and 1971 Supply and Co.
- Owned the creative process from brief through final product and worked closely with Merchandising, Business Management and Marketing teams to ensure my work delivered positive business outcomes.
- Worked closely with UX and Engineering teams when designing websites to make sure users had the most seamless and optimal experience on the web stores. Developed branding guidelines and templates for new clients.

Graphic Designer

Boxport

2005 – 2006

 Performed a variety of creative tasks including designing corporate materials, product photography, image editing and retouching for both web and print.

Print Designer CMP Media Drive Magazine Paradises ink!

2002 – 2007

- Produced page layouts for magazine articles and advertorials, as well as designing ad banners for advertisers.
- Focused on creating appealing presentations through image choice, editing, and clean design.
- · Worked closely with managers and copywriters to deliver quality work.

Education

University of California at Santa Cruz 1996 – 2000 Bachelor of Art: Digital Media and Photography